<?xml version="1.0"?>

<!--
  Alarm dictionary entry for DiameterLB alarms 
-->
<alarm-dictionary type="System" source="DiameterLB">

  <alarm code="150" severity="Alarm" name="ServerOverload">
    <message>Server overload detected</message>
    <description>
      This alarm notifies the operator that the Diameter LoadBalancer has detected a server overload.
      When this situation occurs, the Diameter LoadBalancer starts discarding client requests progressively to preserve the servers.
    </description>
    <corrective-action>
      None on the Diameter LoadBalancer. Some analysis should be done on the server side.
    </corrective-action>
  </alarm>

  <alarm code="151" severity="Alarm" name="ClientOverload">
    <message>Client overload detected</message>
    <description>
      This alarm notifies the operator that the Diameter LoadBalancer has detected a client overload.
      When this situation occurs, the Diameter LoadBalancer starts discarding messages targeted to the client.
    </description>
    <corrective-action>
      None on the Diameter LoadBalancer. Some analysis should be done on the client side.
    </corrective-action>
  </alarm>

  <alarm code="152" severity="Alarm" name="TcpClientDisconnected">
    <message>TCP client disconnected</message>
    <description>
      This alarm is triggered when a client-side TCP connection is closed, regardless of the cause.
    </description>
    <corrective-action>
      None on the Diameter LoadBalancer. Some analysis may be done on the client side. This alarm is not cleared automatically.
    </corrective-action>
  </alarm>
  
  <alarm code="161" severity="Alarm" name="SctpClientDisconnected">
    <message>SCTP client disconnected</message>
    <description>
      This alarm is triggered when a client-side SCTP connection is closed, regardless of the cause.
    </description>
    <corrective-action>
      None on the Diameter LoadBalancer. Some analysis may be done on the client side. This alarm is not cleared automatically.
    </corrective-action>
  </alarm>
  
  <alarm code="162" severity="Event" name="SctpAddressUnreachable">
    <message>SCTP address unreachable</message>
    <description>
      This alarm is triggered when an address of a client-side SCTP connection becomes unreachable.
    </description>
    <corrective-action>
      None on the Diameter LoadBalancer. Some analysis may be done on the network elements. This alarm is cleared automatically when the address becomes available again or when the connection is closed.
    </corrective-action>
  </alarm>
  
</alarm-dictionary>
